A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Staff Subject Files, Kilolo Kijakazi FA1848
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Working Files and Ford Foundation Initiatives, 1987-2014; 1; 37.3 Cubic Feet
  - Convening of Social Security Experts, 2003-2005; 13
    - Kilolo Kijakazi's Background Paper for Convening, 2004 May 5 (Box 29, Folder 281)
    - Wendell Primus' Feedback, 2004 May 14 (Box 29, Folder 282)
    - Progressivity and Saving: Fixing the Nation's Upside Down Incentives for Saving, Peter Orszag and Joseph A. Pechman, Testimony Before the House Committee on Education and the Workforce, 2004 February 25 (Box 29, Folder 283)
    - The Saver's Credit: Issues and Opinions, William G. Gale, J. Mark Iwry, and Peter R. Orszag, 2004 April (Box 29, Folder 284)
    - Michael Sherradan's Seminar on Savings, Asset Building and Social Security, 2004 May 5 (Box 29, Folder 285)
    - Institutions and Inclusion in Saving Policy, Michael Sherraden and Michael S. Barr, 2004 March 4 (Box 29, Folder 286)
    - Oneida Trust Fund, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 287)
    - People with Disabilities and Savings, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 288)
    - Expenses, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 289)
    - Schedule and Transcript, 2004 May 5 (Box 29, Folder 290)
  - Heartland Alliance for Human Needs and Human Rights - Illinois Asset Building Group (IABG), 2004-2012; 14
    - Illinois Asset Building Group (IABG) and Racial Wealth Gap, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 352)
    - Illinois Asset Building Group (IABG) Asset Poverty in Illinois, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 353)
    - Heartland Alliance for Human Needs and Human Rights - Illinois Asset Building Group (IABG) Proposal Information, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 354)
    - Heartland Alliance for Human Needs and Human Rights - Illinois Asset Building Group (IABG) - Recommendation for Presidential Approval Organizational Grant, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 355)
    - Heartland Alliance for Human Needs and Human Rights - Illinois Asset Building Group (IABG) Working File, 2008-2012 (Box 37, Folder 356-359)
    - Poverty Scorecard 2007 Rating Members of Congress, Shriver Center, State of Poverty Campaign, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 360)
    - Learning Circle: Putting Challenges on the Table, The First Meeting of the Learning Circle, Shriver Center, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 361)
    - Heartland Alliance for Human Needs and Human Rights - Illinois Asset Building Group (IABG) Working File, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 362)
    - Woodstock Institute Conversation with Dory Rand, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 363)
    - Illinois Asset Building Group - Background Information, 2004-2007 (Box 38, Folder 364)
    - Consumer Federation of America, Sargent Shriver National Center on Poverty and Law, and Illinois Asset Building Group - Background Information, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 365)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research (IWPR), 2000-2013; 15
    Grant Number 10700520, For a group of women leaders and expert advisors to examine the changing role of women since Social Security was first designed and develop a consensus approach to the modernization of family benefits
    Grant Number 10551113, For research and to produce and disseminate educational materials to help women, their advocates and policy makers understand the impact of the current Social Security system and proposed reforms on women
    - Fact Sheets, 2007-2012 (Box 39, Folder 373)
    - FY 2012 Request 116756 (Box 39, Folder 374)
    - FY 2011 Working File 112471, 2011-2013 (Box 39, Folder 375)
    - Working File FY 2007, 2006-2011 (Box 39, Folder 376)
    - Institute for Women's Policy Research (IWPR) and National Council of Women's Organizations (NCWO) Working File, 2000-2007 (Box 39, Folder 377)
  - Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies, 2005-2013; 16
    Grant Number 08800571, 1988 April 01-1993 December 31
    Support for permanent endowment fund and a reserve fund to address special needs and new program opportunities
    - FY 2013 Request 118965 (Box 40, Folder 382)
    - Civic Engagement and Governance Institute and African American Economic Summit, 2011 (Box 40, Folder 383)
    - FY 2012 Request 116753, 2013 (Box 40, Folder 384)
    - Working File 115021, 2011-2013 (Box 40, Folder 385)
    - Working Files, 2005-2010 (Box 40, Folder 386, Box 41, Folder 387-390)
    - Assessment of Financial Status and Optional Responses, 2007-2008 (Box 41, Folder 391)
    - Funders Briefing at Ford, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 392)
    - Grant 08800571 Status Report, 2008 February (Box 42, Folder 393)
      Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies (08800571), 1988 April 01-1993 December 31
    - Memos, Financial Reports, and Strategic Plan, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 394)
    - Meeting and Agreement, 2007-2008 (Box 42, Folder 395)
    - Memo to Pablo Farias, 2007 September (Box 42, Folder 396)
    - Annual Dinner, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 397)
    - Financial Review Findings Memo, Dennis Shine, Raffa, PC, 2007 August 3 (Box 42, Folder 398)
    - Conversation with Ralph Everett, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 399)
    - Financial Challenge, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 400)
    - Publications, 2009-2010 (Box 42, Folder 401)
  - National Council of Negro Women (NCNW), 2005-2014; 17
    - Working Files and Grant Requests, 2006-2014 (Box 43, Folder 408-409, Box 44, Folder 410-411)
    - Concerns about Leadership Changes, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 412)
    - Policy Work, 2005-2007 (Box 44, Folder 413)
    - Social Security Initiative, 2005-2009 (Box 44, Folder 414)
  - National Asset Scorecard for Communities of Color (NASCC), 2009-2014; 18
    - Duke Data Analysis, 2013-2014 (Box 44, Folder 415)
    - Duke University Data Collection, 2012-2014 (Box 45, Folder 416-417)
    - Duke University - Working Files, 2010-2014 (Box 45, Folder 418-420)
    - Duke University - Questions and Concerns - University of Virginia Center for Survey Research, 2013 (Box 46, Folder 421)
    - Duke University - University of Virginia Survey Research Instrument Pre-test - Grant 11000917, 2011 (Box 46, Folder 422)
      For the Samuel DuBois Cook Center on Social Equity to expand its National Asset Scorecard for Communities of Color, an analysis of wealth disparities across racial and ethnic groups
    - Duke University Site Visit, 2011 December (Box 46, Folder 423)
    - Duke University Boston Fed, 2011-2012 (Box 46, Folder 424)
    - Meeting with Merle Lawrence, 2010 (Box 46, Folder 425)
    - Duke University - Sandy Darity Racial Wealth Gap Scorecard, 2009 (Box 46, Folder 426)
    - New School Working File, 2010-2011 (Box 46, Folder 427)
    - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) Scorecard on the Racial Wealth Gap, 2009-2012 (Box 46, Folder 428)
  - Southern Regional Asset Building Coalition (SRABC), 2010-2013; 19
    - Funder Breakfast: Building a Lifetime of Economic Security: Mobilizing for Change, Jacksonville, Florida, 2013 October 16-18 (Box 59, Folder 556)
    - Funder Breakfast: The Alabama Asset Building Coalition, Flash memory: USB (Box 59)
    - Louisiana Building Economic Security Together (LABEST), 2013 June (Box 59, Folder 557)
    - Site Visit, 2013 September 24-25 (Box 59, Folder 558)
    - City of Baton Rouge Metropolitan Council Certificate of Recognition Presented to Kilolo Kijakazi, 2013 June 4 (Box 60, Folder 559)
    - Getting Equity Advocacy Results (GEAR) Training Notes, 2013 October (Box 60, Folder 560)
    - Site Visits, 2010-2012 (Box 60, Folder 561-563)
    - Federation of Southern Cooperatives Asset Building Project: How Do Low Income People of Color Perceive Assets?, undated; DVD (Box 60)
    - Southern Regional Asset Building Coalition: Asset Building and the Farm Bill: An Untapped Resource, undated; DVD (Box 60)
    - Southern Regional Asset Building Coalition: In Honor of Kilolo Kijakazi, undated; DVD (Box 60)
    - 2011 Partners Meeting, 2010 (Box 61, Folder 564-565)
    - Group Photo with Secretary of Agriculture, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 566)
    - Kilolo's Calls with Coalitions and Feedback, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 567)
    - Coalition for a Prosperous Mississippi Newsletters, 2011-2013 (Box 61, Folder 568)
  - Insight Center for Community Economic Development, 2001-2014; 20
    Grant Number 10500526, 2005 March 01-2009 December 31
    To explore strategies for expanding asset building approaches in the United States with a particular focus on communities of color
    Grant Number 10101235, 2001 May 01-2005 January 31
    To serve as managing partner for the Foundation's initiative on savings and wealth building
    - Publications, 2007-2012 (Box 62, Folder 569)
    - Closing the Racial Wealth Gap Capitol Hill Summits, 2009-2011 (Box 62, Folder 570)
    - Closing the Racial Wealth Gap, New York City, 2007 October 29-30 (Box 62, Folder 571)
    - Closing the Racial Wealth Gap: Perspectives of Experts of Color, Santa Barbara, California, 2006 December 4-6 (Box 62, Folder 572)
    - Asset Building: The Perspective of People of Color, Kellogg Conference Center, Tuskegee University, 2005 October 2-4 (Box 63, Folder 573)
    - Savings and Asset Building: Research, Program Development, Policy Analysis, and Decision-Making in Communities of Color, Tuskegee Convening at Kellogg Conference Center, 2004 May 14-16 (Box 63, Folder 574)
    - Working Files, 2007-2014 (Box 63, Folder 575-576, Box 64, Folder 577-579, Box 65, Folder 580)
      Grant 0130-1385
    - Women of Color Committee and Policy Committee, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 581)
    - Site Visit, 2010 March 26 (Box 65, Folder 582)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) - Working File (Grant 1050-05262), 2005-2007 (Box 65, Folder 583-585)
      Insight Center for Community Economic Development (10500526), 2005 March 01-2009 December 31
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) - Working File (Grant 1010-1235), 2001-2005 (Box 65, Folder 586-587)
      National Economic Development and Law Center (10101235), 2001 May 01-2005 January 31
    - Wealth Gap Working File (Grant 1050-05262), 2008 (Box 66, Folder 588)
  - Asset Funders Network (AFN), 2012-2014; 21
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Meetings, 2012 (Box 54, Folder 511)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Conference Call, 2013 November 19 (Box 54, Folder 512)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Guiding Principles, 2013 November (Box 54, Folder 513)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Webinar, 2013 November 7 (Box 54, Folder 514)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Conference Call, 2013 September 17 (Box 54, Folder 515)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Bay Area Network Meeting, 2013 September 10 (Box 54, Folder 516)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Co-Chairs Calls, 2013-2014 (Box 54, Folder 517)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Tax Policy Project Charter, 2012 (Box 54, Folder 518)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Call Notes, 2013 (Box 54, Folder 519)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Conference and Group Meeting, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 520)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Tax Policy Projects, 2012 (Box 55, Folder 521)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Call with Dorothy Brown, 2012 July (Box 55, Folder 522)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Guiding Principles, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 523)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Selection of Project Manager, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 524)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Eugene Steuerle, Urban Institute and Tax Policy Center, 2012 (Box 55, Folder 525)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Conversations on Tax Reform Collaboration, 2012 (Box 55, Folder 526)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Amanda Feinstein, Bay Area Network and Bob Friedman, Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED), 2012 (Box 55, Folder 527)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Steering Committee Meeting, 2013 October 2 (Box 55, Folder 528)
    - Grantmaker Webinar Series: The Web of Wealth: Resiliency and Opportunity, or Driver of Inequality?, 2014 (Box 55, Folder 529)
    - Tax Policy Project (TPP) Transition, 2014 (Box 55, Folder 530)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Conference Call, 2014 June 27 (Box 55, Folder 531)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Webinar on the Tax Policy Project: Seizing the Moment, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 532)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Call, 2014 June 3 (Box 55, Folder 533)
    - Tax Policy Project (TPP) Webinar for Funders, 2014 (Box 56, Folder 534)
    - Tax Policy Project (TPP) - Calls and Articles, 2013-2014 (Box 56, Folder 535)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Meeting, 2014 (Box 56, Folder 536)
    - Tax Policy Advisory Group (TPAG) - Call with Alan Jenkins and Heather McCulloch, 2014 (Box 56, Folder 537)
  - Urban Institute, 2004-2014; 22
    Grant Number 10551335, 2005 August 01-2006 July 31
    For research and dissemination to educate the public about the nature of the protections in the current Social Security system and the impact of proposed reforms on beneficiaries
    - Opportunity, Ownership, and Retirement Security Proposal, 2014 (Box 66, Folder 592)
    - Assets, Tax Reform, and Connecting Research to Policy and Practice Proposal, 2013-2014 (Box 66, Folder 593)
    - Savings, Social Insurance, and the Safety Net: The Complementary Roles of Public and Private Approaches to Helping Families Weather the Economic Downturn Proposal, 2012 (Box 66, Folder 594)
    - A Primer on the Dynamic Simulation of Income Model (DYNASIM3) Discussion Papers, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 595)
    - Working Files, 2007-2011 (Box 67, Folder 596-598)
    - Opportunity and Ownership Over the Life Cycle Convening, 2008 May 28 (Box 67, Folder 599-600)
    - Roundtable on Asset Building for Low- and Moderate-Income Families: Strengthening Private Sources of Retirement Income, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 601)
    - Evaluation of Assets for Independence Program, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 602)
    - Site Visit, 2012 (Box 68, Folder 603)
    - Social Security Research (Grant 1055-1335), 2005-2006 (Box 68, Folder 604)
      The Urban Institute (10551335), 2005 August 01-2006 July 31
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL), 2011-2014; 23
    - Flash Drive with Zip File of 2014 BESOL Convening, Flash memory: USB (Box 68)
    - Loose Flash Drive Related to Zip File of 2014 BESOL Convening, Flash memory: USB (Box 68)
    - 2014 Convening - Agenda and Handouts (Box 68, Folder 605)
    - 2014 Convening - Kilolo's Welcome and Introduction of Research Panel (Box 68, Folder 606)
    - 2014 Convening - Agenda (Box 68, Folder 607)
    - 2014 Convening - Event Planning Meeting (Box 68, Folder 608)
    - 2014 Convening - Research Panel Prep Call (Box 68, Folder 609)
    - 2014 Convening - Communicating Research to Target Audiences (Box 68, Folder 610)
    - 2014 Convening - Talking Points for Introduction of Melvin Oliver (Box 68, Folder 611)
    - 2014 Convening - Advocacy at the National, Regional, State, and Local Levels Panel (Box 68, Folder 612)
    - 2014 Convening - Closing Keynote, Maya Wiley (Box 68, Folder 613)
    - 2014 Convening - Intro for Xav De Souza Briggs' Keynote (Box 68, Folder 614)
    - 2014 Convening - Evaluation (Box 68, Folder 615)
    - 2014 Convening - Speakers and Moderators (Box 68, Folder 616)
    - 2014 Convening - Call with Toni Cooke (Box 68, Folder 617)
    - 2014 Convening - Realize Consulting Group Correspondence (Box 68, Folder 618)
    - 2011 Grantee Convening at Ford - Information Binder (Box 69, Folder 619)
    - 2013 Convening - Logistics, Menu, and Agenda, 2012-2013 (Box 69, Folder 620)
    - 2013 Convening - Notes on Sessions (Box 69, Folder 621)
    - 2013 Convening - Kilolo's Remarks (Box 69, Folder 622)
    - 2013 Convening - Remarks and Presentations (Box 69, Folder 623)
    - 2012 Grantee Convening - Agenda, Participants, Grantee Reports, and Notes (Box 69, Folder 624)
    - 2013 Convening - Draft Agenda and Planning Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 69, Folder 625)
    - 2012 Grantee Convening - Logistics and Planning (Box 70, Folder 626)
    - 2011 Grantee Convening - Evaluation and Handouts (Box 70, Folder 627)
    - Evaluation - Monitoring Template and Survey - Drafts, Revisions, and Correspondence, 2011-2012 (Box 89, Folder 789-790, Box 90, Folder 791)
    - Evaluation - Grantee Feedback, 2011-2012 (Box 90, Folder 792)
    - Evaluation - Grantee Meeting, 2011 July (Box 90, Folder 793)
    - Evaluation - Initiative Summary and Outcome Documents Submitted to Pablo Farias, 2011 (Box 90, Folder 794)
    - Evaluation - Proposal Meetings, 2009-2011 (Box 90, Folder 795)
    - Evaluation - U.S. Rural Livelihood Initiative Summary, 2011 September 15 (Box 90, Folder 796)
    - Evaluation - Amy Brown's Theory of Change (TOC) Map, 2011 (Box 90, Folder 797)
    - Evaluation - Theory of Change Guides, Notes, and Presentation, 2009 (Box 90, Folder 798)
    - Communications - Kilolo's Presentation to Ford Staff on Communications Strategy, 2013 October 30 (Box 90, Folder 799)
    - Communications - Douglas Hattaway PolicyLink Communications Webinar - Persuading 7 Out of 10 Americans to Support Financial Security and Ideas for Changing the National Dialogue About Government Asset Building Efforts, 2012-2013 (Box 90, Folder 800)
    - Communications - Message Manual, Hattaway Communications - Drafts and Correspondence, 2012 (Box 90, Folder 801)
    - Communications - Communications Workshop and Speech Coaching: Bringing Your Message to Life, Asset Building Programs and Policies: Developing a Motivating Message, and Message Manual Revisions, 2012 (Box 91, Folder 802)
    - Communications - Hattaway Communications and Greenberg Quinlan Rosner (GQR) Research - Ford Asset Strategic Research, 2012 (Box 91, Folder 803)
    - Communications - Asset Building Programs and Policies: Developing a Motivating Message, Hattaway Communications, 2012 May 10 (Box 91, Folder 804)
    - Communications - Workshop, 2012 April (Box 91, Folder 805)
    - Communications - Success Measures: Measuring Outcomes of Financial Capability Programs: Success Measures Tools for Practitioners, NeighborWorks America and Citi Foundation, 2011 (Box 91, Folder 806)
    - Communications - Focus Group Notes, 2011-2012 (Box 92, Folder 807-808)
    - Q and A, 11309, Hathaway Communications, G1, 5:30pm, KC (Kansas City) Residents, 2011 August 30; DVD (Box 92)
    - Q and A, 11309, Hathaway Communications, G2, 8:00pm, KC (Kansas City) Residents, 2011 August 30; DVD (Box 92)
    - Q and A, 11309, Hathaway Communications, G3, 5:30pm, KC (Kansas City) Residents, 2011 August 31; DVD (Box 92)
    - Q and A, Hathaway Communications, G4, 8:00pm, KC (Kansas City) Residents, 2011 August 31; DVD (Box 92)
    - Communications - Alan Jenkins' Comments, 2011 (Box 92, Folder 809)
    - Communications Infrastructure, 2009-2011 (Box 92, Folder 810)
  - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC), 2004-2005; 24
    Grant 10101235, 2001 May 01-2005 January 31
    - Invitees for Tax Individual Development Account (IDA) Children's Savings Accounts (CSA) Convening, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 295)
    - Saving and Asset Building Grantee Convening, Draft Agenda, 2005 June 16 (Box 30, Folder 296)
    - Tuskegee First Convening, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 297)
    - Christine Robinson, Stillwaters Consultation, 2004 April (Box 30, Folder 298)
    - Tax Policy Convening, 2004 June 15 (Box 30, Folder 299)
    - Focus Groups for Program Officer Memo (POM) by National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC), 2004 (Box 30, Folder 300)
    - Grant Number 1010-1235-1, 2001-2004 (Box 30, Folder 301-302)
    - Ford Foundation Saving and Investment Strategies, Focus Group Demographics, Summaries, Notes, and Questions, 2004 July 9 (Box 30, Folder 303)
    - Ford Foundation Saving and Investment Strategies, Notes and Background Materials from Convenings, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 304-305)
    - Ford Foundation Saving and Investment Strategies, Report to Kilolo Kijakazi, 2004 July (Box 31, Folder 306)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) - Individual Development Account (IDA) Practitioner, Oakland, California - Anouk, Susie, 2004 April 2; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15861)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
      Restricted pending further processing
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) - Individual Development Account (IDA) Practitioner, Los Angeles, California - Anouk, Susie, 2004 April 21; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15862)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) - Individual Development Account (IDA) Practitioner, Lansing, Michigan - Michigan IDA Partnership - Anouk, Susie, 2004 June 4; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15863)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) - Individual Development Account (IDA) Participant, Los Angeles, California - New Economics for Women - Anouk, Susie, 2004 April 24; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15864)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) - Individual Development Account (IDA) Participant, Oakland, California - Lao Family Com. Dev. Inc. - Anouk, Susie, 2004 May 6; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15865)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) - Individual Development Account (IDA) Participant, San Antonio, Texas (Part 1) - Dept of Community Initiatives - Anouk, Susie, 2004 June 30; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15866)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) - Individual Development Account (IDA) Participant, San Antonio (Part 2) - Dept of Community Initiatives - Anouk, Susie, 2004 June 30; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15867)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) Mixed Race, Oakland, California - Lao Family Community Dev. Inc. - Anouk, Susie, 2004 March 27; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15868)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) English-Speaking Cambodian and Laotian, Asian Immigrants, Oakland, California (1 of 3) - Lao Family Com. Dev. Inc. - Anouk, Susie, 2004 April 3; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15869)
      English speaking - Cambodian and Laotian
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?), Vietnamese with Translator, Asian Immigrants, Oakland, California (2 of 3) - Lao Family Com. Dev. Inc. - Anouk, Susie, 2004 April 3; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15870)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) Chinese with Translator, Asian Immigrants, Oakland, California (3 of 3) - Lao Family Com. Dev. Inc. - Anouk, Susie, 2004 April 3; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15871)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) Latino Americans, Los Angeles, California (1 of 2) - New Economics for Women - Anouk, Susie, 2004 April 24; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15872)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) Latino Americans, Los Angeles, California (2 of 2) - New Economics for Women - Anouk, Susie, 2004 April 24; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15873)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) African Americans, Atlanta, Georgia - Atlanta Neighborhood Development Partnership - Anouk, Susie, 2004 May 13; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15874)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) Native Americans Umatilla Indian Reservation, Oregon - Umatilla Reservation Housing Authority - Anouk, Susie, 2004 June 1; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15875)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Recorded double time